{
    "subject": "resource/E._M._S._Namboodiripad",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Madras_Presidency",
    "human_readable": "E.M.S. Namboodiripad was born in Madras Presidency.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9179697632789612,
            "question": "Where was E.M.S. Namboodiripad born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9006766676902771,
            "question": "In what year was E.M.S. Namboodiripad born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7232746481895447,
            "question": "What is E.M.S. Namboodiripad known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5878850221633911,
            "question": "What political party was E.M.S. Namboodiripad associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5854423642158508,
            "question": "How did E.M.S. Namboodiripad influence Indian politics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5407893061637878,
            "question": "What is the legacy of E.M.S. Namboodiripad in India?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5337287783622742,
            "question": "Did E.M.S. Namboodiripad hold any high political offices?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.532796323299408,
            "question": "What were some of E.M.S. Namboodiripad's major contributions?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4387374818325043,
            "question": "What was the historical context of E.M.S. Namboodiripad's life and work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4281390905380249,
            "question": "What are some key events or movements associated with E.M.S. Namboodiripad?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=E.M.S. Namboodiripad was born in Madras Presidency.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6788_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the historical context of E.M.S. Namboodiripad's life and work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6788_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were some of E.M.S. Namboodiripad's major contributions?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6788_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did E.M.S. Namboodiripad hold any high political offices?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6788_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6788_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6788_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6788_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6788_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6788_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6788_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6788_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6788_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6788_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6788_59.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```  \n\n\nE.M.S. Namboodiripad was born in Perinthalmanna, Kerala. The documents do not mention Madras Presidency. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that according to the documents, EMS Namboodiripad was born on June 13, 1909, at Elamkulam, Perinthalmanna taluk, Malappuram (document 1), and also in Perintalmanna taluk of the present Malappuram district into an aristocratic upper-caste Brahmin family (document 2). There is no mention of him being born in Madras Presidency."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided documents do not contain any information about E.M.S. Namboodiripad's birthplace being the Madras Presidency. The context mentions that he was born on June 13, 1909, in Perinthalmanna, Malappuram district, Kerala, India, which contradicts the statement that his birthplace was the Madras Presidency."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "E.M.S. Namboodiripad was born in Perinthalmanna, which is not part of the Madras Presidency. Instead, it is a town located in the present-day Malappuram district of Kerala, India.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Several sources state he was born in Perinthalmanna, Kerala.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information states that E M S Namboodiripad was born at Elamkulam, Perinthalmanna taluk, Malappuram, and also mentions that he was elected to the Madras Legislative Assembly in 1939, but this does not necessarily imply that he was born in Madras Presidency.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information clearly states that E.M.S. Namboodiripad was born on 13 June 1909, at Elamkulam, Perinthalmanna taluk, Malappuram district in Kerala, not in the Madras Presidency.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}